http://www.caledonianrecord.com/site/privacy.html

CaledonianRecord.com Privacy Statement
CaledonianRecord.com and the other newspapers and Web sites of Caledonian-Record Publishing Company, Inc. – are committed to protecting your privacy online.
Not only does protecting your personal information help you, but it increases consumer confidence and hopefully your participation online.
The purpose of this policy to let you know what information we gather about you when you visit our sites, how we use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone and the choices you have about those functions.
Our sites may have links to other Web sites. We have no control over the content or privacy practices of any of these sites or those of our business partners or advertisers.Cookies
Our sites use cookies. Cookies help our Web sites recognize you as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while you were visiting. A cookie cannot get any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. We track the number of unique visitors to our sites and which articles or sections receive the most visitors, but not by any personally identifiable information. If you choose to modify your browser preferences to reject all cookies, you may have difficulty navigating our sites.Information We Collect
You may be asked to voluntarily supply some personal information, including your name and contact information. If you choose to supply this information via the Internet know that we will never sell or share your personal information. We use the information you supply us to perform statistical analysis and marketing breakdowns. Some of our Web sites collect information as part of a reader advisory group. We may use that information to target questions of a specific nature to interested participants. If you elect to receive any of our electronic newsletters via e-mail or the e-mail breaking news service, we may use that address to invite you to participate in a readers group or some similar newspaper function.Advertisers
The Caledonian-Record Web sites will perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in different portions of our Web site and to inform advertisers about how many consumers have clicked on their ads. We only disclose information to third parties in aggregate form. Personal information about you will not be provided.E-mail
The Caledonian-Record may use the e-mail addresses collected to send you promotional e-mail about services offered by The Caledonian-Record or its advertisers.
We may contact you regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, or to confirm your login information.Accuracy of Information
You may use the feedback form on our sites to provide us with any changes in your information at any time. Or, if you prefer, direct questions regarding our privacy policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of the information we collect by e-mail to the Web Department at webdept@caledonian-record.com. You may reach us by telephone at (802) 748-8121 or by mail at:
The Caledonian-Record 190 Federal St. P. O. Box 8 St. Johnsbury, VT 05819Use of Materials
The right to download and store or output the materials in our sites is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of The Caledonian-Record is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact the Web Department at webdept@caledonian-record.com.This privacy policy is effective as of January 1, 2015. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and will post those changes here as soon as they take effect.
Coronavirus Impact
World carbon dioxide emissions drop 7% in pandemic-hit 2020
Exposure feared after New Hampshire speaker dies of COVID-19
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
Daily Headlines
Today's top headlines from the Caledonian-Record.
Breaking News
Breaking News alerts from The Caledonian-Record news team.
Business Week
The latest business news from the Northeast Kingdom, North Country and beyond.
Coronavirus: The Latest Updates
The latest coronavirus news from The Caledonian-Record, and Vermont, New Hampshire, and national news sources.
You must select at least one email list.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Visit Auto802.com to shop and compare local new and used vehicles.
COPYRIGHT CALEDONIAN RECORD PUBLISHING COMPANY, INC 2016 | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
